Exercise 7-7 Consistent Pronoun Stress in Changing Verb Tenses This is the same as
the previous exercise, except you now stress the verbs. They eat them. Practice
this until you're quite comfortable with the intonation. Notice that in fluent
speech, the TH of them is frequently dropped, as is the H in the other object
pronouns, him, her. The pronunciation and word connections are on the right, and the
tense name is on the far left. they eat them two they ate them three they're
eating them four they'll eat them five they'd eat them six they'd have eaten them
seven the ones that have eaten them eight they've eaten them nine they'd eaten them
ten they'll have eaten them eleven they ought to eat them Twelve, they should eat
them. Thirteen, they shouldn't eat them. Fourteen, they should have eaten them.
Fifteen, they should have eaten them. Sixteen, they could eat them. Seventeen,
they couldn't eat them. Eighteen, they could have eaten them. Nineteen, they
couldn't have eaten them. Twenty, they might eat them. Twenty-one, they might
have eaten them. Twenty-two, they must eat them. Twenty-three, they must have eaten
them. Twenty-four, they can eat them. Twenty-five, they can't eat them.